Hello everyone, in this video, I'm going to show you how to update and edit
your profile.
So first things first, go to addwork.com and log in with your username and
password.
Once you're all logged in, hover over my details and click edit profile.
So firstly, you want to enter your first and last name.
Use your camera name here, not your real name.
Next, you can add your phone number. Now this is if you want to offer SMS and
phone chat.
And if you do, you put your number here and then you have to verify it.
And just be aware that the clients never actually get your real number.
So, you know, don't worry about having to get a new number or anything like
that.
You can just use your current one and they'll never get your real number, which
is great.
Next you want to add your location. Now, I would always recommend using a
different location
from where you're from and also your hometown on where you're living.
Maybe you're born somewhere and you're living somewhere else, but no matter
what it is,
always use a different location from where you're from and where you're
currently living.
Unless you are offering escort services, then you're going to want to put the
right location.
But if you're not, then choose a different location.
This way, it just keeps things a little bit more discreet.
As you scroll further down at the very bottom here, it's got the AdultWork.com
interview.
Click complete it and there are many different things that you can do here and
write about.
For example, if you click into the about you, you can see there's all different
things to
fill out. It's good to do this because the more the clients feel like they know
about
you, the more stronger their bond is going to be with you.
Once you've done all that, click save. I'm not going to click it now, but I
just wanted
to show you. Next, we're going to click on personal details.
Okay, so here you put your data birth. Again, you can choose a different data
birth to keep
things more discreet. Select your gender that will already be selected for you
when your
profile is made, but just make sure it's showing the right gender.
Okay, so here on the sexual orientation, I've selected bisexual on mine because
this means
I come up in more search results. So if you're comfortable to as well, you can
select bisexual.
So then you're just found a lot easier and come up on more searches for more
clients.
And this be here where it says, "I enjoy the following." Again, tick as many as
possible,
as many as you're comfortable with, as that way you just come up in more search
results.
To be honest, a lot of these things I wouldn't actually do on cam, but I just
tick it anyway
because just because it's tick, it doesn't mean you have to do it. You know, it
could
just mean you're going to discuss it on cam or you never even have to do it or
discuss
it with some of them. It just means you come up in more searches. So the more
ticks, the
better. Of course, there's some that I wouldn't take. For example, lacking/lact
ating because
of course, I'm not pregnant. But if I was, I would tick that. I wouldn't tick
being
filmed because I never want the clients to think they're going to film me. So
yeah,
just go through them all and tick as many as you're comfortable with. And also
down here
at the bottom, this is who you would do it with. I have all my ticks. I've just
noticed
they've added a new one, so I'm just going to tick that one as well. Even
though I wouldn't
do those things with two males or a female male, whatever, it doesn't matter.
It's all
fantasy and it just means I'm coming up in more search results. Okay, so now I
'm moving
on to the About You section. Here, you're going to have a short summary. And
then in
this be here is your main bio. So you want to kick this out and write as much
in here
as possible. And don't worry at the beginning, if you don't really know what to
write. You
can just write something basic in there and ask your mentor to help you. This
is something
you will develop over time. So don't feel like you have to write a huge amount
of text
if you're not really sure what to write. Because as your webcam persona
develops over time,
so will this. Just so you know as well here, you can actually click on to this
and it'll
show you that there's different things you can add onto your bio. So you can
add a tab,
you can make the text in bold or italic, you can add emojis. So all of this
stuff I recommend
doing because it just makes your profile look a little bit more eye-catching.
And once you've
done that, you can hit save and view. So as you can see, this is how it looks.
Some bits
are in bold. I have a tab. So yeah, you can work on your own and add in as much
as you
like. So let's go back to updating the profile. So we're going to go back onto
my details
and then click edit profile. And now we go along to the pictures tab. Okay, so
here are
your three main profile pictures. This is where you will upload them. And you
just quite
straightforward, click on choose file and then select whatever photo you want.
For your
main one, your first one here, we recommend using a photo where you take up
most of the
photo. So for example, as you can see my profile pictures here, let me zoom in.
This one, I
know they look a bit blurry there, but they don't look like that on the screen.
It's just
because I'm zooming in. This one, as you can see, I'm taking up most of the
screen, whereas
this one, I'm just, you know, quite far back. And that's why I chose this one
as the first
one and this one as the second one. Because when you are on cam, you are only
going to
be a small thumbnail on a large, on a screen with all different girls on there.
So you
want to make sure that your photo is eye-catching as possible and you are taken
up as much of
the photo as possible. So you're seen more by the clients. If you need any help
or advice
on what profile picture is best to select, please just ask us and we'll give
you our
best advice. Okay, so once you've uploaded the photos, you will then click here
on manage
consent and another window will pop up. Okay, I'm not sure it's not actually
going to show
it now because I don't have any consent to give, but usually it will say
profile pictures
and then it will have a little free next to it and you click on the free and
then it will
tell you you need to give consent for those new photos you just put on and it's
basically
just given consent that it is you and you are happy for those photos to be
uploaded. I've
already given consent that's why nothing's come up here but just always know
whenever
you upload any photos or videos, not just your profile pictures but any
pictures at all,
you have to give consent for everything otherwise they don't upload and this is
where you do
it here. Okay, and as we scroll down, we can now take a look at where we upload
our free
gallery, private gallery and movie clips. So your free gallery is able to be
viewed by
the clients for free, so don't put pictures in here that are revealing but do
put a few
in there and then you can also take a look at the private gallery and upload
some pictures
into that. The more pictures you have, the more you can charge so the clients
actually
have to pay to see this one so you can literally make money while you sleep and
in here I would
use more revealing photos and if you are uncomfortable to have that kind of
stuff on your profile,
they'll make a private gallery but just be aware that you won't be able to
charge as
much and finally you can upload some movie clips as well and you can charge for
every
single clip. So the more you have on there, the more opportunities you have to
make money
while you're not even online as your clients can buy these when you're not
online and of
course you can always direct your regular clients to go view your private
gallery and
go view your movies and that way it's just bumping up your weekly pay. Just
another
note as well with the private gallery, when uploading the pictures I recommend
writing
a caption for every photo because the clients, before buying it, they will see
the captions
before they see the photos. So if you write really entice and captions then the
clients
will think oh wow I really want to see this private gallery, it sounds like the
pictures
in there are amazing. So they'll buy it whereas if you don't write any captions
at all they
might not be drawn in to buy it. Again just hit save and view once you've done
all of
that and just to reiterate and make sure you always give consent for all of the
pictures
and videos that you upload. So if you click here you can see my free gallery, I
've actually
got a lot in there and also the private gallery and finally we'll go back to
edit profile
and click here on the webcam tab. If you click here on edit direct cam settings
, okay so
this is where we edit all of the settings regarding our price per minute if we
want
to do free chat and also our strap line. Okay so here is where we turn on free
chat if we
want it on and then turn it off again. Never click this one, guess free preview
. This basically
means that people who don't even have any credits in their account or don't
even have
an account can see you, we don't want this. So I would never recommend taking
this one
but if you do want to turn on free chat you can click this one here. Breath the
moment
and I haven't got mine on and here is where we click for our group and private
chat and
set our rate per minute. You'll already be set a rate per minute that we set
for you
and it will be on the lower end of the scale as it will be a brand new profile
but as you
become more established on there and build up your profile, build up your
feedback and
your regulars you can then up your price. And finally here you will select what
category
you want to be in so I put myself in the DOM category but you can also put
yourself in
categories regarding age so you know depending on whether you're a teen 20, 30,
40 mature
if you're a couple profile this is what you'll select here or if you're more of
a fetish
base profile then you'll click one of the fetishes here. And one last thing on
here
to note is your stop line. So every time you go online I would recommend
updating your
stop line. Now this is the clients will see this when you're on the main page
of all the
other girls so they'll see your profile picture, your name and then if they
hover over your
profile picture your stop line will come up. So I wrote a mine come see me in
my new sexy
laundry set so I must have had a new laundry set on that day when I ripped that
one and
you can write whatever you want and you can also take a look at what the other
girls are
writing on the website to get some inspiration but again you want this to be as
eye-catching
as possible just so the clients are intrigued by this and then they want to
come and come
you and when you're finished press save. There's one more thing I would like to
add
and every single time you go online I would recommend clicking on to this bit
here and
changing something in your bio it might just be an exclamation mark here it
might be a
whole new paragraph you know it could be anything but just update it no matter
what it is because
if you update this then you come up in the top of search results so like I said
even if
it's just something like you know adding an extra full stop or whatever just
make sure
you update it and yeah it just fits well for you when you're going online as
you come up
in more stitches and finally I just wanted to let you know there actually are
many more
things you can add to your profile you can add a wishlist and you can sell
stuff there's
so many more things that you can do but these are the basics that we recommend
starting
with and then as you build your profile and as you you know get more familiar
with the
website we can then show you how to add more to it but if you do what is said
in this video
this is a very very good foundation to work with I hope all that made sense and
if you
have any questions at all please don't hesitate to ask we are here to help you
and guide you
and yeah just give you as much advice as possible so I hope that helped and I
'll see you on
the next video.